RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977
  - Education (Box 90)
    - Greater Hartford Community College (B) (Box 91)
    - Groton Vocational Technical School (B) (Box 91)
    - Hartford State Technical Schools (Box 91)
    - Harvard (Box 91)
    - Higher Education (B) (Box 92)
    - Higher Education Employment Contracts (B) (Box 92)
    - Higher Education - Misc. Information (Box 92)
    - Horace Wilcox Vocational Technical School (Box 92)
    - Housatonic C.C. (Box 92)
    - Housatonic Community College - Letters in regard to need for new campus (B) (Box 92)
    - Independent colleges (B) (Box 93)
    - Intercollegiate Student Legislature (B) (Box 93)
    - Litchfield High School (B) (Box 93)
    - Manchester Community College (B) (Box 93)
    - Master Plan (B) (Box 93)
    - Mattatuck Community College (B) (Box 93)
    - Memos to and from Commissioner Sheld (Box 93)
    - Middletown Community College (Box 93)
    - Minority Involvement in Higher Education (B) (Box 93)
    - Miscellaneous Information (I) (Box 93)
    - Miscellaneous material (Box 93)
    - Mohegan Community College (B) (Box 94)
    - Mohegan Community College Audit (Box 94)
    - Mount Holyoke College (Box 94)
    - Mystic Oral School (B) (Box 94)
    - Mystic Oral School Mag. (B) (Box 94)
    - National Council on Education Research (Box 94)
    - National Youth Service (O) (Box 94)
    - Naugatuck Valley Higher Education Center (B) (Box 94)
    - New Britain Teachers’ Dispute (B) (Box 94)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 94)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 94)
    - New Haven Teachers’ Strike (B) (Box 94)
    - Noroton School (B) (Box 94)
    - Northwestern Community College (B) (Box 94)
    - Norwalk Community College (B) (Box 94)
    - Norwalk State Technical College (B) (Box 95)
    - Nursing Education/State Assistance (B) (Box 95)
    - Oak Hill School for the Blind (Box 95)
    - Occupational Training Grant (B) (Box 95)
    - Office of Veterans Affairs (B) (Box 95)
    - Osteopathic School (B) (Box 95)
    - Parent Teacher Association (Box 95)
    - Parochial Schools (B) (Box 95)
    - Partners of the Americans (Box 95)
    - Pending (B) (Box 95)
    - Platt Regional Vocational School (B) (Box 95)
    - Press Release CHE (Box 95)
    - Press Release from Governor’s Office (Box 95)
    - Project Matthew (Box 95)
    - Quinnebaug Valley Community College (Box 95)
    - Quinnebaug Valley C.C. Concerning Land Acquisition (B), 1975 November (Box 95)
    - Quinnebaug Valley Community College Site (O) (Box 96)
    - Quinnebaug Valley Community College - Tx’s to Members of Ad Hoc Site Committee (O) (Box 96)
    - Quinnipiac (B) (Box 96)
    - Sacred Heart (B) (Box 96)
    - Scholarship Commission (Box 96)
    - School Breakfast Program (Box 96)
    - School Bus (B) (Box 96)
    - School Construction (B) (Box 96)
    - School Finance Advisory Panel (B) (Box 96)
    - School Financing (B) (Box 96)
    - School Funding - Haton Case (Box 96)
    - School Lunches (B) (Box 96)
    - Services for the Blind (B) (Box 96)
    - South Central Community College (B) (Box 97)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (B) (Box 97)
    - SCSC - Ethnic Heritage Studies (Box 97)
    - Special Education (Box 97)
    - Special Education: (Box 97)
    - A-D (B) (Box 97)
    - E-H (B) (Box 97)
    - I-M (B) (Box 97)
    - N-R (B) (Box 97)
    - S-Z (B) (Box 97)
    - Special Education #5 (B) (Box 97)
    - Special Education Cost Committee Meeting, 1977 January 28 (Box 97)
    - State Board of Education (B) (Box 97)
    - State Board of Education Meetings (Box 97)
    - State Colleges (B) (Box 98)
    - State College M. Majeske (B) (Box 98)
    - Student Loans Higher Education (B) (Box 98)
    - Teacher Ed. Pilot Project (B) (Box 98)
    - Teacher Retirement (B) (Box 98)
    - Teacher Retirement Mag. - September 16 (Cost of Living increases) (B) (Box 98)
    - Teachers’ Strike (B) (Box 98)
    - Teachers’ Strike/General Mag. (B) (Box 98)
    - Teachers’ Strike/Shelton Mag. (B) (Box 98)
    - Technical Colleges (B) (Box 98)
    - Technical Colleges Mag. Card (B) (Box 98)
    - Technical School - Mag. Card (B), 1984 August 15 (Box 99)
    - Technical Schools - Mag. Card for Petition and Blue Collar Worker (I) (Box 99)
    - Technical Schools - Printed letter, 1975 August (Box 99)
    - Technical - Vocational Colleges, 1975 August (Box 99)
    - Themes Valley State Technical (B) (Box 99)
    - Transition Task Force for Education (I) (Box 99)
    - Truman Scholarship Fund (B) (Box 99)
    - Tuition (B) (Box 99)
    - Tunxis Community College (Box 99)
    - University of Bridgeport (B) (Box 99)
    - UCONN (Box 99)
      - A (B) (Box 99)
      - B (B) (Box 99)
      - C (B) (Box 99)
      - D (B) (Box 99)
      - E (B) (Box 99)
      - F (B) (Box 100)
      - G (B) (Box 100)
      - H (B) (Box 100)
      - I, J (B) (Box 100)
      - K (B) (Box 100)
      - L (B) (Box 100)
      - M (B) (Box 100)
      - N (B) (Box 100)
      - O (B) (Box 100)
      - P (B) (Box 100)
      - Q, R (B) (Box 100)
      - S (B) (Box 100)
      - T (B) (Box 100)
      - U, V (B) (Box 100)
      - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 100)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 May 14 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees of the University Hospital (Box 102)
    - Branches, closing (B) (Box 102)
    - CREUES, Center for Real Estate and Urban (Box 102)
    - Economic Studies/ Annual Report (Box 102)
    - Civil Preparedness (B) (Box 102)
    - Concern for the Branches #25 (B), 1977 March 8 (Box 102)
    - Daily Campus (Box 102)
    - Dental School (B) (Box 102)
    - Finance Committee Board of Trustees Minutes, Financial Report (B), 1973-1974 (Box 102)
    - Food Service (Box 102)
    - Graduate Library (B) (Box 103)
    - Groton Branch (Box 103)
    - Hartford Seminary Letter #28 (B), 1977 November (Box 103)
    - Health Center (Box 103)
    - Health Center Advisory Council (Box 103)
    - Home Economics School (B) (Box 103)
    - Hospital Board of Trustees, Minutes of Meeting (Box 103)
    - Internal Auditor’s Report (Box 103)
    - John Dempsey Hospital (Box 103)
    - Law School (B) (Box 103)
    - Law School - Purchase of Hartford Seminary Petitions Answered by Postcard, 1977 September (Box 103)
    - Legislation, 1975 (Box 104)
    - Library (B) (Box 104)
    - Marijuana Course (B) (Box 104)
    - Medical School (B) (Box 104)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1975 January - May (Box 104)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees - Minutes (Box 105)
    - Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1975 December - 1976 June (Box 106)
    - Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1976 September - 1977 June (Box 107)
    - Misc. Material (Box 108)
    - Nursing (B) (Box 108)
    - Operating Budget, 1976 - 1977 (Box 108)
    - PRIG (Box 108)
    - Psychiatry (Box 108)
    - Puerto Rican Center (B) (Box 108)
    - School Of Agriculture (Box 108)
    - Special Commission to establish & detail the purposes and goals for the UCONN Health Center (O) (Box 108)
    - Stanford Campus (B) (Box 108)
    - Torrington Branch (B) (Box 108)
    - Torrington Branch Mag. Card (B) (Box 108)
    - Water Resources, Mag. Sept. 18 (B) (Box 108)
    - Waterbury Branch (B) (Box 108)
    - Work - Study (Box 108)
  - Education: - University of Hartford: (Box 108)
    - Vet. College (Box 108)
      - A (B) (Box 108)
      - B (Box 108)
      - C (Box 108)
      - D (Box 108)
      - E (Box 108)
      - F (Box 109)
      - G (Box 109)
      - H (Box 109)
      - I, J (Box 109)
      - K (Box 109)
      - L (Box 109)
      - M (Box 109)
      - N (Box 109)
      - P (Box 109)
      - Q, R (Box 109)
      - S (Box 109)
      - T (Box 109)
      - W, X, Y, Z (Box 109)
    - [Vet. College] Board of Registration and Examination (Box 109)
    - Vet. College (Misc. Mat.) (Box 109)
    - Vet. Medicine (B) (Box 109)
    - Vet. Medicine, Commission on Alternatives (Box 109)
    - Vet. School/Mag. Card/New England Regional College of Veterinary Medicine (I), 1975 June 25 (Box 109)
    - Vet. School/New Letter/Renegotiating spaces (B), 1975 May (Box 109)
    - Vinal Tech in Essex (O) (Box 109)
    - Vocational and Rehabilitative Education (B) (Box 109)
    - Vocational Education (B) (Box 109)
    - Vocational Education Budget Cuts (B) (Box 110)
    - Voc. Ed. Master Plan (Box 110)
    - Vocation Rehabilitation (B) (Box 110)
    - Vocational/Technical Advisory Committee (B) (Box 110)
    - Voc./Tech Misc. material (Box 110)
    - Waterbury Higher Education Center (B) (Box 110)
    - Waterbury Inquiry (Box 110)
    - Waterbury State Technical Colleges (B) (Box 110)
    - Waterbury Technical School (B) (Box 110)
    - Western Conn. State College (B) (Box 110)
    - Western Conn. State College Concerning Construction (I) (Box 110)
    - Wethersfield Law School (B) (Box 110)
    - Windham Regional technical School (B) (Box 110)
    - Wisconsin System (Box 110)
    - Wolcott Technical School (B) (Box 110)
    - Wright Technical School (B) (Box 110)
  - Education - Yale (Box 111)
  - Elected Officials (Box 111)
  - Elections (B) (Box 111)
  - Elections (B) (Box 111)
  - Elections Commission (B) (Box 111)
  - Elections Commission - Ambrogio Assignment (B) (Box 111)
  - [Elections Commission] - Anon. Anti Ambrogio Letter (Box 111)
  - Elections - Special (B) (Box 111)
  - Elections Statistics (Box 111)
  - Electric Boat (B) (Box 112)
  - Electrical Examiners (B) (Box 112)
  - Electronic Fund Transfers, National Commission on (Box 112)
  - Elevator Installation, Repair and Maintenance Work (O) (Box 112)
  - Examining Board (Box 112)
  - Embalmers and Funeral Directors (B) (Box 112)
  - Employment (Box 112)
    - A-L (B) (Box 112)
    - M-Z (Box 112)
  - Endorsements (B) (Box 112)
  - Endorsements (B) (Box 112)
  - Energy (Box 112)
    - A (B) (Box 112)
    - B (B) (Box 113)
    - C (B) (Box 113)
    - D (B) (Box 113)
    - E (B) (Box 114)
    - F (B) (Box 114)
    - G (B) (Box 114)
    - H (B) (Box 114)
    - I, J (B) (Box 114)
    - K (B) (Box 115)
    - L (B) (Box 115)
    - M (B) (Box 115)
    - N (B) (Box 116)
    - O, P (B) (Box 116)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 116)
    - S (B) (Box 117)
    - T (B) (Box 117)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 118)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 118)
  - Energy (Box 118)
    - Advisory Board (Box 118)
    - Agency/Annual Report (Box 118)
    - Agency/Letters to Private Enterprise (B) (Box 118)
    - Agency/Memos (Box 118)
    - Agency/Press Releases (Box 118)
    - Agency/Speaking Engagements (Box 118)
    - Alaska Natural Gas Transportation (Box 118)
    - Alcan Pipeline (Box 118)
    - Artic Natural Gas - 34c (B), 1977 July 8 (Box 118)
    - Assistance Program (B) (Box 118)
    - Assistance Program/Letter to Congressional Delegation (O) (Box 118)
    - Assistance Program/Tx’s for Participation (O), 1977 October 5 (Box 118)
    - Atomic Energy Act (B) (Box 118)
    - Conservation (B) (Box 119)
    - Conservation/Funding for Community Services Administration (I) (Box 119)
    - Conservation Program (Box 119)
    - Conservation Program Feasibility Report (Box 119)
    - Court Cases (Box 119)
    - Crisis Intervention (O) (Box 119)
    - Crisis Management Program (Box 119)
    - Crisis Management Program (O) (Box 119)
    - Electrical Energy Needs #65 (B) (Box 119)
    - Emergency Fuel Bank (B) (Box 119)
    - Emergency Fuel Funds/Letters to Cong. Delegation (O), 1977 March 8 (Box 119)
    - Emergency Plan (Box 119)
    - Emergency Plan, 1975 January 15 (Box 119)
    - Federal Energy Adm. Grant (Box 119)
    - Federal Energy Agency (B) (Box 119)
    - Federal Energy Guidelines (Box 120)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Comm. (I) (Box 120)
    - Governor’s Energy Project (Box 120)
    - Invitation to Forum on President Carter’s Energy Program (O) (Box 120)
    - Letter sent out by OPM to all Towns (O) (Box 120)
    - Letter sent to Cong. Delegation/Winter Summary (O) (Box 120)
    - Material (Box 120)
    - Memo/Radioactive material (O) (Box 120)
    - Memos to and from Brooks (Box 121)
    - Memos to and from Harrison (Box 121)
    - Misc. material (Box 122)
    - Misc. material (Nuclear) (Box 122)
    - National Energy Act (B) (Box 122)
    - Natural Gas (B) (Box 122)
    - New England Energy Material (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Materials/Briefing, 1977 August 2 (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council (O) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council/ (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Plant #64 (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Plants #64 (B), 1977 April 13 (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Reactors (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (B) (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Safety Task Force (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Waste #38 (B) (Box 122)
    - Oil Refinery (Box 122)
    - Oil Tanker Terminal (B) (Box 122)
    - Omnibus Energy Bill (Box 122)
    - Planning and Energy Policy (B) (Box 122)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s office (Box 122)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council Mag. Letter, 1975 August 8 (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Power Plant #64 (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Power Plants #64, 1977 April 13 (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Reactors (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Safety Task Force (Box 123)
    - Nuclear Waste (Box 123)
    - Oil Refinery (Box 123)
    - Energy/Oil Tanker Terminal (Box 123)
    - Planning and Energy Policy (Box 123)
    - Omnibus Energy Bill (Box 123)
    - Energy Press Releases from Governor’s office (Box 123)
    - Seabrook (B) (Box 124)
    - Telegram to president Concerning Emergency Allocation Act (Box 124)
    - Westledge Center for Education (DPEP) (Box 124)
  - Engineers (B) (Box 124)
  - Environment (DEP) (Box 124)
    - A (B) (Box 124)
    - Ba-Bk (Box 125)
    - Bl-Bz (B) (Box 125)
    - C (Box 126)
    - D (Box 126)
    - E (Box 126)
    - F (Box 127)
    - G (Box 127)
    - H (Box 128)
    - I, J (B) (Box 128)
    - K (Box 128)
    - L (Box 128)
    - Ma (Box 128)
    - Mc (B) (Box 129)
    - Me (B) (Box 129)
    - N (B) (Box 129)
    - O (B) (Box 129)
    - P (B) (Box 130)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 130)
    - S (B) (Box 131)
    - T (B) (Box 131)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 132)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 132)
  - Environment (DEP) (Box 132)
    - Aerosol Cans (B) (Box 132)
    - Air Compliance (Box 132)
    - Air Pollution (B) (Box 132)
    - Algae Control (B) (Box 132)
    - Anti-Hunting (B) (Box 132)
    - Application of NELCO & CLP (Box 132)
    - Atlantic States Maine Fisheries Comm. (Box 133)
    - Audubon (Box 133)
    - Auto Emissions (B) (Box 133)
    - Automobile Pollution Strategies (Box 133)
    - Bantam Lake (B) (Box 133)
    - Batterson Park (B) (Box 133)
    - Beaches (B) (Box 133)
    - Beaches/Mag. Card (B) (Box 133)
    - Beaches & Ned Coll #53A (Box 133)
    - Berkshire - Litchfield Council (Box 133)
    - Black Rock State Park (Box 133)
    - Bluff Point (B) (Box 133)
    - Boating (B) (Box 133)
    - Boating at Pachaug Pond (B) (Box 133)
    - Branford Pollution Control (B) (Box 133)
    - Branford Salt Marsh (Box 133)
    - Bride Brook (Box 133)
    - Bridgeport Hydraulic Co.. - Policy on Surplus Land (Box 133)
    - Byram River (Box 133)
    - Camping (B) (Box 133)
    - Candlewood Lake (Box 133)
    - Citizens Bulletin (Box 133)
    - Clean Air Act (B) (Box 133)
    - Clean Air Act/to Congressional Delegation (O) (Box 133)
    - Closed (Box 133)
    - Coastal Zone Management (B) (Box 133)
    - Collector Sewers (Box 133)
    - Commission on Environmental Protection and Economic Development (O) (Box 134)
    - Commissioner Gill Appointment (B) (Box 134)
    - Complimentary Licenses (O) (Box 134)
    - Concorde (Box 134)
    - Conn. Environmental Policy Act (O) (Box 134)
    - Conn. Environmental Policy Act (Box 134)
    - Conn. Resources/Recovery Authority (B) (Box 134)
    - CRRA/Housatonic Valley Council (B) (Box 134)
    - Conn. River Basin (B) (Box 134)
    - Conn. River Gateway Commission (B) (Box 134)
    - Conn. River Valley Flood Commission (Box 134)
    - Conn. River Watershed Council (Box 134)
    - Conservation and Development Plan (Box 134)
    - Conservation Officers (B) (Box 134)
    - Conservation and Preservation (Box 134)
    - Conservation and Preservation Revenue (Box 134)
    - Container Deposit/Summary of Legislation (Box 134)
    - Cos Cob (B) (Box 134)
    - Council on Environment Quality (Box 135)
    - Council on Water Company Lands (Box 135)
    - Danbury Land Fill (Box 135)
    - Dinosaur State Park (B) (Box 135)
    - Diversion of Conn. River (B) (Box 135)
    - Diversion of Water from Conn. River at Northfield Mountain in Mass. - letter to Congressional Delegation (O) (Box 135)
    - Dog Racing Facility - Shelton (Box 135)
    - Dog Track (Box 135)
    - Dredging (Box 135)
    - Dredging - Themes River #33 (B) (Box 135)
    - Dredging - Themes River Project (B) (Box 135)
    - Earthquake Victims - Haly (B) (Box 135)
    - Endangered Species (Box 135)
    - Environment Committee (Box 135)
    - Environment Meeting Mag. Card, 1977 February (Box 135)
    - Environment News (Box 135)
    - Environmental Caucus (Box 136)
    - Environmental Committee, 1/2, Mag. Card (O) (Box 136)
    - Environmental Concerns (Box 136)
    - Environmental Education (B) (Box 136)
    - Environmental Groups, Dec. 16 - Mag. Card (O) (Box 136)
    - Environmental Health (Box 136)
    - Environmental Impact Statements (O) (Box 136)
    - Environmental Quality control (Box 136)
    - Equine Council (Box 136)
    - Executive Order (Box 136)
    - Farmington River Valley (B) (Box 136)
    - Federal DEP (Box 136)
    - Fish & Game (B) (Box 136)
    - Fishway (B) (Box 136)
    - Floods (B) (Box 136)
    - Fluorocarbons (Box 136)
    - Fresh River (B) (Box 136)
    - Geological Survey (Box 136)
    - Gillette Castle (Box 136)
    - Grant Applications (B) (Box 136)
    - Griswold Airport (Box 136)
    - Groton Sewers (Box 136)
    - Hammonasset (B) (Box 136)
    - Harbor Development (Box 136)
    - Harkness Memorial (Box 136)
    - Housatonic Basin Project (B) (Box 136)
    - Hunting (B) (Box 137)
    - Indians (Box 137)
    - Indirect Source (Box 137)
    - Inspection and Maintenance Program (B) (Box 137)
    - Ivy Mountain Farm/ Town of Groton (Box 137)
    - King’s Mark (Box 137)
    - Lakeridge (Box 137)
    - Land Acquisition Unit (Box 137)
    - Land Conservation (Box 138)
    - Land Donation (B) (Box 138)
    - Land Gifts - Preservation (Box 138)
    - Landfill Mag. Card (I) (Box 138)
    - Landfill in Seymour/Beacon Falls area (B) (Box 138)
    - Land use (Box 138)
    - Legal Department (B) (Box 138)
    - Legislation (Box 138)
    - Litter (B) (Box 138)
    - Lobster (B) (Box 139)
    - Long Island Sound (Box 139)
    - Long Island Sound Regional Study (Box 139)
    - Marine (B) (Box 139)
    - Mashamoquet State Park (Box 139)
    - Memos (Box 139)
    - Memos to and from Brampton (Box 140)
    - Memos to and from Gill (Box 140)
    - Memos to and from Greg Sharp (Box 140)
    - Memos to and from IPAC (Box 140)
    - Memos to and from Schneidermeyer (Box 141)
    - Meshomasic State Forest (Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 141)
    - Middletown Race Track (B) (Box 141)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Plant Petition (B), 1977 October 7 (Box 141)
    - Millstone Point (Box 141)
    - Mohawk Mountain Ski Area (Box 141)
    - Motor Vehicle Emission (Box 141)
    - Mystic River/Wetlands Application - Mag. Card (Box 141)
    - National Wild and Scenic River System (Box 141)
    - Natural/National Resource Council (Box 141)
    - Navigable Waters (Box 141)
    - New England Advisory Board for Fish & Game (Box 141)
    - New England Fisheries Steering Committee (Box 141)
    - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control (Box 141)
    - New England River Basin Commission (Box 142)
    - News Clippings (Box 142)
    - Niantic Farm (Box 142)
    - Noise Pollution (B) (Box 142)
    - Noroton River (B) (Box 142)
    - Northwestern Conn. Lakes/Mag. (B) (Box 142)
    - Norwalk River (Box 142)
    - Oil Refinery (B) (Box 142)
    - Oil Spills (Box 142)
    - Open Space in Seymour (O) (Box 142)
    - Open Spaces (B) (Box 142)
    - Outdoor Recreation (Box 142)
    - Outdoor Recreation - Mag. (B), 1976 January (Box 142)
    - Outer Continental Shelf - New England Seacoast (B) (Box 142)
    - Park River Local Protection Project (I) (Box 142)
    - Parks (B) (Box 142)
    - Park & Forests (B) (Box 142)
    - Pending (B) (Box 142)
    - Pesticides - Uses and Users (Box 143)
    - Pitch In/ Brooklyn Killingly Scout Troops (Box 143)
    - Point West (B) (Box 143)
    - Pollution (Box 143)
    - Pollution Letters/ Petition by Hadassah (O) (Box 143)
    - Preservation and Conservation (B) (Box 143)
    - Press Releases (Box 143)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 143)
    - Pro Bampton (B) (Box 143)
    - Pro Gill (Box 143)
    - PT Barnum Housing Project (Box 143)
    - Public Hearings (Box 143)
    - Public Works Projects (B) (Box 143)
    - Radiation Sources and Radioactive Materials (Box 143)
    - Rainbow Dam (B) (Box 143)
    - Recreation (B) (Box 143)
    - Recycling (B) (Box 143)
    - Report on Conduct of DEP Employees (Box 143)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act of 1976 (RCRA) (Box 143)
    - Rocky Neck (Box 143)
    - Rooster River (B) (Box 144)
    - Route 7 (Box 144)
    - Septic System Regulation (Box 144)
    - Sewers (B) (Box 144)
    - Shepaug River (B) (Box 144)
    - Sherwood Island State Park (B) (Box 144)
    - Silver Sand State (Park) Mag. (B) (Box 144)
    - Soil Conservation (B) (Box 144)
    - Solid Waste (Box 144)
    - Solid Waste Management and Advisory Council (Box 144)
    - Solid Waste Management and Advisory Council - People who resigned (O) (Box 144)
    - Stanford Water Pollution (Box 144)
    - State Air Quality Implementation Plan (Box 144)
    - Steel Brook (B) (Box 144)
    - Stony Creek Quarry (Box 144)
    - Sulphur (Box 144)
    - Talmadge-Ann. Amendment/Water pollution- Letter sent to Delegation (B), 1975 August 11 (Box 144)
    - Transportation Control Plan (Box 144)
    - Trumbull Lake Project (Box 144)
    - United States Environmental Protection Agency (Box 145)
    - Waste Treatment Grant (Box 145)
    - Water Company Lands (Box 145)
    - Water Compliance (Box 145)
    - Water Funds/Mag. 208 (B), 1975 September 11 (Box 145)
    - Water Pollution (Box 145)
    - Water Pollution Control Act (Federal) (Box 145)
    - Water Pollution Control Project (Box 145)
    - Water Pollution 208 Funds - Letter to Congressional Delegation, (B) (Box 145)
    - 1975 June 23 (Box 145)
    - Water Resources (Box 145)
    - Water Supplies (Box 145)
    - West Rock State Park (B) (Box 145)
    - Wet Lands (B) (Box 145)
    - Wildlife (B) (Box 145)
    - Wolcott Race Track (B) (Box 146)
    - Yantic River Flood Control Project (Box 146)
    - Yantic River Watershed (Box 146)
  - Epilepsy Commission (Box 146)
  - Equal Rights (B) (Box 146)
  - Ethics (B) (Box 146)
  - Executive Orders (Meskill’s) (Box 146)
  - Fairfield Speech, 1975 September 9 (Box 146)
  - Fairfield Visit (B) (Box 146)
  - Family Planning Reporter (Box 146)
  - Family Relations (B) (Box 147)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (B) (Box 147)
  - Federal Bureau Of Investigation (B) (Box 147)
  - Federal Communications Commission (Box 147)
  - Federal Council for Science and Technology (Box 147)
  - Federal Elections Commission (Box 147)
  - Federal Funding (B) (Box 147)
  - Federal Government (B) (Box 147)
  - Federal Grants (Box 148)
  - Federal I.C.C. (Box 148)
  - Federal Legislation (B) (Box 148)
  - Federal Matter (Box 148)
    - A (B) (Box 148)
    - B (B) (Box 148)
    - C (B) (Box 148)
    - D (Box 148)
    - E (B) (Box 148)